Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/brandon-penner-a47128a3 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Negotiation Marketing Retail

Brandon Penner

Night Floor Manager at Costco Wholesale Surprise, Arizona, United States

Summary

Experienced Front End Supervisor with a demonstrated history of working in the retail industry. Skilled in Negotiation, Budgeting, Customer Service, Retail, and Sales. Strong sales professional with a Bachelor's Degree focused in Global Business / Finance from Arizona State University.

Experience

Costco Wholesale

7 years 7 months

Night Floor Manager November 2022 - Present (1 year)

Surprise, Arizona, United States

Front End Supervisor April 2016 - Present (7 years 7 months)

The Roomstore of Arizona Merchandiser June 1997 - April 2016 (18 years 11 months)

Education

Arizona State University

Bachelor's Degree, Global Business / Finance · (2004 - 2006)

Glendale Community College

Associate's Degree, Global Business · (2002 - 2004)

Glendale Community College

Associate's Degree, General Studies · (1999 - 2002)